# **Sedry Muhammad Iqbal**

Mobile Phone: +6281912474614 E-Mail: sendrym94@gmail.com

github.com/sedryiqbal | linkedin.com/in/sedryiqbal/

#### Objective

I am a graduate of the Sriwijaya State Polytechnic majoring in Computer Engineering and have experience in the field of Engineering and Information Technology. I can work in a team, think creatively, focus on areas that use logic and problem solving skills, communicate well, and be ready to take on new challenges and have a purpose in every decision. I also like to learn new things, anything can be learned as long as there is an intention, because of the effort and belief that I can do it.

#### Education

 State Polytechnic of Sriwijaya, Palembang, Indonesia A. Md. T.(3.39/4.0) August 2019 - August 2022

Related Course: Computer Engineering

Final Report : Electrical Workshop Equipment Sterilization System Using UV-C Light Sterilization Box Based on Internet Of Things (IoT)

State Vocational High School 1

Related Course: Network Computer Engineering

Expertise Competency Exam: Installation and Configuration of Wired and Wireless Computer Network Devices (Mikrotik)

### **Related Activity**

Komunitas Tim Robot Polsri
Member Programmer Divisi Krsbi Beroda 2019-2020
Head Of Division Krsbi Beroda 2021-2020

November 2019 - Juli 2022

#### Achievment:

Kontes Robot Indonesia Regional and Nasional: By Pusat Prestasi Nasional conducted online

- Top 5 Best Participants of KRSBI Regional
- Participants of KRSBI Nasional
- Himpunan Mahasiswa Jurusan Teknik Komputer Member Humas 2019-2020

August 2019 - August 2022

Head Of Department PSDM 2021-2022

- List students who have achievements in both academic and non-academic fields so that they can be managed by the department to be included in competitions in each
- Create a learning forum, namely Student Study Groups (KSM) called CESSGO where there are several areas of learning related to computer engineering majors with mentors from seniors who previously had potential in their fields. Building relationships and intimacy with new students.

### **Work Experience**

Project Based Learning, Palembang, Indonesia Mentor Synapse Academy

Core Responsibilities

February 2022- March 2022

Private Class Project Based Learning, Case Study Based Learning, at that time I became a mentor in learning the basic programming language C++. My job is to teach and practice the basic material of C++ programming.

### Software Engineer Freelance

### Core Responsibilities

I have a team who works with independently on several projects as software engineer.
The projects such as Embedded Systems, Robotics, IoT (Internet of Things), and Computer Vision.

### **Internship Experience**

Lembaga Layanan Pendidikan Tinggi Wilayah II, Palembang, Indonesia

Staff Sumber daya August 2021 – Oktober 2021

## Core Responsibilities

- Maintain computer hardware and printers
- Input monthly archive data for determining the credit score for functional positions of lecturers in 4 regions of the Province of Bangka Belitung, Bengkulu, Lampung, South Sumatra
- Create a Website Development Project for Lecturer Scholarship Recommendation Service Standards.

#### **General Qualification**

- Experienced in Information Technology research, basic low voltage (DC) electricity, Robotics, IoT (Internet of Things), Computer Vision and has basics in computer science such as: Operating System Installation | Application installation, computer troubleshooting both hardware and software.
- Have people management skills, and Good Leadership in entry-level positions in Tech Industry.
- Basic knowledge in programming languages C++, HTML/CSS, Mysql, Python, VB Net and Github.
- have good communication skills and eager to adapt.

#### References

- Malian Zikri, CEO Digital Creative, Sriwijaya University(malianzikri92@gmail.com)
- Areif Rahmansyah, Machine Learning Engineer Gojek, Sriwijaya University(ariefrahmansyah@hotmail.com)
- M. Zafier Faza, Software Developer, PT. indo Arta Teknologi, Sriwijaya State Polytechnic (zafierfazamuhammad@gmail.com)
- Taufiiqul Hakim, Software Engineer | Teaching Assistant at Digital Creative, Sriwijaya State Polytechnic (Taufiiqulhakim23@gmail.com)